

OLEKSANDR **DROHOMYRETSKYI**

Javascript Developer

SKILLS

- NestJS
- ReactJS
- Typescript
- Leadership
- Redux Toolkit
- NextJS
- GraphQl
- Postgresql

- RTK Query
- GitHub/GitLab
- SPA/PWA
- REST API
- Agile practice
- Jira, Trello, Figma
- GraphQl
- Postgresql

EDUCATION & TRAINING

UMCS Lublin

Bachelor of Informatic Mathematic and Physic(Engineer's) 2019 - Ongoing

Okten School

Javascript Fullstack Developer 2020 - 2021

LANGUAGES

- English B1
- Polish C1
- Ukrainian native
- Russian C1

CONTACT

+48 884 879 510

✓ drohomyretskyi.oleksandr@gmail.com

Warsaw

https://alex-bielow.vercel.app/

ABOUT ME

A well-motivated developer, with over 3+ years' experience as full-stack developer. Successfully implemented wide range of projects from web services to large web platforms. Acted as a team leader and was involved in direct communication with end-client to propose obstacles resolution. Participated in the entire software delivery process of getting a software product to customers, from conceptualization, through development, and ending in the actual installation and launching it. Proactive, versatile, highly adaptable, answer finder, intellectually curious.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Expletech

2021 - 2024

Full stack developer - Full time

Website for well-known Cinema with landing page and admin dashboard:
Focused on creating a RESTful API with authentication, integrating AWS S3, a ticket purchasing service, deploying on AWS Elastic Beanstalk, and overseeing frontend development.

Technology stack: NextJS, Redux Toolkit, NestJS, TypeORM, PostgreSQL, TypeScript.

• E-commerce platform for client in Dubai, focused on grocieries delivery from different shops located around the user, project included robust admin dashboard. Efforts were directed towards creating a RESTful API, integrating AWS S3, Stripe for payment processing, obtaining proper geolocation and collaborating with another overseas backend team.

Technology stack: NextJS, Redux Toolkit, NestJS, TypeORM, PostgreSQL, TypeScript.

• Employees oriented social network, a platform which allows user to leave a reviews about employer, salaries and much more. Responsible for team and client communication, participating in development, being main obstacles resolver. Implemented chat, LinkedIn integration, notification system, CMS, and admin panel.

Technology stack: ReactJS, Redux Toolkit, NestJS, TypeORM, Socket.IO, PostgreSQL, TypeScript.

Freelancer

2020 - 2021

Frontend Developer - Part time

 Variety of projecst per client's needs, Participation in startup development and ongoing projects: Contributed to the development of two startup projects and one major commercial project, gaining significant experience in development and problem- solving, deepening understanding of development processes and internal company operations.

REFERENCES

Andrii Debrivskiy

Email: andriy@expletech.com

Expletech / CEO

Oleg Goley

Expletech / CEO

Email: oleg@expletech.com